http://www.pwdfoundation.org/privacy-notice/

Privacy Notice | PWD Foundation, Inc.
Skip to content PWD Foundation, Inc.A Foundation For The Future MenuHomeAboutAbout The FoundationOur Funding StrategyFinancialsBoard of DirectorsNewsletterIn the NewsResearchFunded ResearchGenetic ResourcesGuide to Genetic TestsClear by ParentageTRIBUTESRainbow Bridge PoemLegacy DonorsGeneral TributesDedicated TributesGet InvolvedDonate OptionsSend a CardDonate in TributeLegacy DonationsVehicle Donation ProgramOther Ways to GiveDonate
Search
Search for:
Privacy NoticeYour privacy is important to the Portuguese Water Dog Foundation, Inc. (“PWD Foundation”).  This Privacy Notice describes the data we collect, use, disclose, transfer and store your information.  By using this Site, you consent to the data practices described in this Privacy Notice.This Privacy Notice does not apply to other sites that may be accessible through the PWD Foundation site. Our Site contains links to other websites that are operated by third-parties. You are encouraged to read the privacy notices of those other sites to learn how they collect and use the data collected about you.The PWD Foundation may change this Privacy Notice at any time and for any reason. If there are changes to this Privacy Notice, we will post those changes here with a “last update date” of when the Privacy Notice was revised.Information CollectedCookiesThis Site uses “cookies” that are used to collect site information about your online activity. A “cookie” is a small text file that is stored on your device. The data collected may include your domain name, host for Internet access, date and time of your access, your computer’s IP address including its operating system and browser, and the pages you visit. We may also use web beacons to help compile analytics, which may be from third-party service providers.You have the ability to control cookies and similar technologies.  If you choose to block cookies from our Site, some features of our Site may not function properly.Online DonationsYou are allowed to make online donations on our Site. The PWD Foundation collects the following information through our online financial-transaction pages: name, address, email address, phone number and credit card information. This is personally identifiable information and may be provided to a third-party in order to facilitate the transaction, acknowledge receipt of your donation, as well as include you on our mailing list, if you choose to join it.If you send a donation as a tribute of someone and request that an acknowledgement be sent to another individual, we will use their name and address of the individual for acknowledgement purposes only.EmailYou have the opportunity to receive email communications from us. If you provide us with your email address, you will be automatically registered to receive our email newsletter. You may unsubscribe from this email newsletter at any time by clicking the opt-out link included in every email newsletter that we send.SurveysYou may be asked to complete survey questions that appear on our Site. The information from these surveys is used in aggregate. We generally do not ask for information in surveys that would personally identify you. However, if we do request contact information, you may decline to provide it. Your information and all data from surveys are confidential.Sharing of InformationWe do not share, sell, or rent the personal information you provide to us to third-parties, except as described below.We may share your personal information that you provided to us with service providers we have retained to perform services on our behalf. These service providers are contractually restricted from using or disclosing the information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or to comply with legal requirements.We may disclose information about you (i) if we are required to do so by law or legal process, (ii) to law enforcement authorities or other government officials as required to comply with a legitimate legal request, or (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary to prevent physical harm or financial loss, or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity.SecurityWe know that the security of your personally identifiable information is important. We provide reasonable controls to protect your personal information. However, no data transmission over the Internet is 100% effective and we cannot ensure or warrant the security of such information.ChildrenThe PWD Foundation does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we inadvertently collect personal information from a person under the age of 13, we will use commercially reasonable efforts to delete it.Contact UsIf you have any questions regarding our Privacy Notice, please contact us.PWD Foundation, Inc.P. O. Box 203Parker Ford, PA 19457-0203info@pwdfoundation.orgLast Updated: 4/29/2015FacebookIn the News Research Update CHF-02107 Mid-Year: Landmark Clinical Trial to Establish the Evidence-Based Use of Regenerative Medicine to Treat Tendon Injury in Dogs Research Update Mid-year 3 CHF 02428: Identifying the Disease-Defining Autoantibodies in Canine Addison’s Disease Research Update Mid-year 3 CHF 02519: Prevalence of Bartonella spp. Infection in Dogs with Cardiac and Splenic Hemangiosarcomas Within and Between Geographic Locations Research Update Mid-year 3 CHF 02488: Addison’s Disease and Symmetrical Lupoid Onychodystrophy in Bearded Collies Provide Common Ground for Identifying Susceptibility Loci Underlying Canine Autoimmune DisordersSubscribe to our newsletter Get the latest Portuguese Water Dog Foundation news delivered right to your inbox! Enter your email address below.
Leave this field empty if you're human: About UsPortuguese Water Dog Foundation, Inc. P.O. Box 203 Parker Ford, PA 19457-0203 (610) 707-2589PRIVACY NOTICE TERMS OF SERVICE CONTACT US Privacy Notice ©
Copyright 1998-2020 | Portuguese Water Dog Club of America, Inc. | A 501(C)(3) not-for-profit organization. | All rights reserved.
We use cookies to ensure that you get the best experience. By clicking 'Accept' on this banner, or using our site, you indicate that you have read our Privacy Notice.
Accept
Close GDPR Cookie Settings
Privacy Overview
Strictly Necessary Cookies
Privacy OverviewThis website uses cookies so that we can provide you with the best user experience possible. Cookie information is stored in your browser and performs functions such as recognising you when you return to our website and helping our team to understand which sections of the website you find most interesting and useful.
Strictly Necessary CookiesStrictly Necessary Cookie should be enabled at all times so that we can save your preferences for cookie settings.
Enable or Disable Cookies
If you disable this cookie, we will not be able to save your preferences. This means that every time you visit this website you will need to enable or disable cookies again.
Enable All Save Changes
